<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Janet Brady: artist</title>
    <link>//artistjanet.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Janet Brady: artist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 20:15:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//artistjanet.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>//artistjanet.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 20:15:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//artistjanet.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m wondering as I walk… could this mean disaster! I see settlements and trackways making patterns which evolve and dissolve in time. I see patterns in natural landscapes which evolve and dissolve too. Over millennia life comes and goes leaving a particular stamp on Place. The place leaves its own mark on the people too.
Brief summary of my journey into the artworld&amp;hellip; After many years teaching myself the basics of drawing and painting I have been lucky enough to go on some good courses with Hazel Campbell and Lee Crocker and Steve Walton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Techniques and media</title>
      <link>//artistjanet.com/page/techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 20:15:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//artistjanet.com/page/techniques/</guid>
      <description>Doodling at school under the desk&amp;hellip; funny to see their influence still coming through! Drawing with pencil, pastels pen and charcoal of course but more unusually with a laboratory dropper and inks &amp;ndash; love that Watercolours &amp;ndash; often very wet and fluid&amp;hellip; sometimes incorporating raindrops! Inks &amp;ndash; same. I could mention here my delight in preparing the first layer with inks etc worked and moved with clingfilm Some oils but as I&amp;rsquo;m often on a walking trip they&amp;rsquo;re not so practical Acrylics I also love sgraffito often in combination with torn and layered paper I also make prints e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neo exhibition</title>
      <link>//artistjanet.com/project/pictures-from-bolton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 17:05:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//artistjanet.com/project/pictures-from-bolton/</guid>
      <description>This collection is from St George&amp;rsquo;s Gallery. Pop into neo: gallery in the MarketPlace&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m proud to be part of this cutting edge contemporary art group!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pembrokeshire</title>
      <link>//artistjanet.com/project/pembrokeshire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 15:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//artistjanet.com/project/pembrokeshire/</guid>
      <description>Here is some work from a short trip in November 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re:allotted</title>
      <link>//artistjanet.com/project/re-allotted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 16:23:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//artistjanet.com/project/re-allotted/</guid>
      <description>Here is some of the work I&amp;rsquo;m exhibiting at St George&amp;rsquo;s Gallery, Bolton this February. I&amp;rsquo;ve made collagraphs out of some sketches I did visiting various allotments.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated to find out about the network of fungi in the soil beneath that lives in a symbiotic relationship with the plants above. It reminds me of the internet and the way we might also live in a symbiotic relationship with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limestone Country Arnside</title>
      <link>//artistjanet.com/project/arnside/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 18:42:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//artistjanet.com/project/arnside/</guid>
      <description>This work is about the ancient limestone landscape around Arnside.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>